{
    "subject": "resource/Pannonia_Savia",
    "predicate": "property/capital",
    "object": "resource/Siscia",
    "human_readable": "Pannonia Savia's capital is Siscia.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.841770350933075,
            "question": "Where was Pannonia Savia's capital located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8389115333557129,
            "question": "What is the capital of Pannonia Savia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8122612833976746,
            "question": "What city served as the capital of Pannonia Savia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.781960129737854,
            "question": "What was the name of the capital city in Pannonia Savia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7800387144088745,
            "question": "Siscia is the capital of which region?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.774196207523346,
            "question": "Name the city that was the center of Pannonia Savia."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.503135085105896,
            "question": "In what location was Siscia situated?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48079943656921387,
            "question": "Which city held administrative power over Pannonia Savia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45642364025115967,
            "question": "Pannonia Savia's governance originated from which city?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43166375160217285,
            "question": "Which city held the political leadership of Pannonia Savia?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Pannonia Savia's capital is Siscia.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7983_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Pannonia Savia's governance originated from which city?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7983_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which city held administrative power over Pannonia Savia?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7983_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what location was Siscia situated?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7983_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7983_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7983_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7983_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7983_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7983_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7983_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7983_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7983_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7983_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7983_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents does not support this triple. While Siscia (Sisak) is mentioned as an important urban center and a former capital of Pannonia Savia, it is not identified as its current capital. In fact, one document suggests that the importance of Sisak declined with the great migration in the 7th century."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Pannonia Savia's capital is Siscia.\" Specifically, document 16 (or 7 and 25) mentions that in the year 297, Colonia Flavia Siscia became the capital town of the Province of Pannonia Savia."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The claim is wrong because Sirmium is the metropolis of the whole Pannonia.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}